



Kyrkogatan 2E, lgh: 1303; 37132, Karlskrona



ahmedjobaer2@gmail.com



Github



Linked-In

EXPERTISE

Python

Groovy

Java J2SE & J2EE

Docker

Kubernetes

Microservice

Jenkins

Spinnaker

EDUCATION

MSc in Software Engineering and Technology at Chalmers University of Technology, Göteborg, Sweden

JOBAER AHMED

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Experienced software engineer with 4+ years of experience focusing on the software development with different programming languages. Confident communicator, strategic thinker, and innovative creator to develop software that is customized to meet a company's organizational needs, highlight their core competencies, and further their success.

EXPERIENCE

Job #1 [June 2021 - Ongoing]

CI/CD Developer at Ericsson AB, Karlskrona

Developing and maintaining automated CI/CD pipelines to facilitate continuous integration, delivery, and deployment of software applications. Writing and optimizing scripts (e.g., Python, Bash) to automate build, test, and deployment processes, ensuring efficient and reliable software delivery. Implementing and configuring containerization technologies such as Kubernetes and Docker to streamline application deployment and scalability. Collaborating with crossfunctional teams to identify bottlenecks in the software delivery lifecycle and implementing solutions to improve speed, quality, and reliability. Utilizing tools like Spinnaker to orchestrate complex deployment strategies, manage releases, and enable seamless rollbacks in case of issues.

Job #2 [September 2018 - November 2019]

Software Engineer at Swisslog Logistics Automation, Partille

Worked with backend and frontend development. Tools & Technology Used: java, Spring, Jboss, json, weblogic, MSSql, jpql, sql, jenkins, subversion, maven, eclipse

Job #3 [June 2018 -- August 2018]

Summer Worker at Ericsson AB, Gothenburg

- -Exploring Testing Strategies for Microservice-Based System In Continuous Delivery (5G)
- -Writing python script to analyze JSON APIs and sorting results